{
    "question": "Complete the sentences with Said or Told !    1.I___ them that I didn`t agree with them\r\n2.Anwar_____ that he couldn`t lend me his book\r\n3. belle ____ the beast that she loved him\r\n4 the poor farmer ____ the Giant that they wanted a child\r\n5. takutaliang ____ that he only brought a doll",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "1.told<br>2.told<br>3.said<br>4.said<br>5.told",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "1. told<br>2. said<br>3. told<br>4.told<br>5. said<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-24-auxiliary-verb-dalam-bentuk-past-tense-dan-present-te-204",
            "question": "Sebutkan 24 auxiliary verb dalam bentuk past tense dan present tense!\r\nDipisah",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "are,be,will,shall,have,has,am,is,do",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kakakaku-minta-contoh-percakapan-tentang-asking-and-giving-facts-481",
            "question": "kakak,aku minta contoh percakapan tentang asking and giving facts dong yg tentang olahraga :) pliss...:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: Hello, What do you know about badminton?<br>B: Badminton is racqued sport, played by two people ( for single ) or two pairs (\u00a0for double ) , are opposite each other.<br>A: Okay, thanks for your information<br>B: You&#039;re welcome",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-ceritakan-kembali-cerita-di-bawah-ini-240",
            "question": "Tolong ceritakan kembali cerita di bawah ini !    \u00a0\r\n\r\n \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 The greedy dog\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 One day, a dog stole a big piece of meat and he was very\r\n proud of it. Then, he ran off until he reached the bank of the river. He looked\r\n down into the river water carefully and he saw another dog with a piece of meat\r\n in its mouth.\r\n\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Funnily enough, the dog did not realize that it was his own\r\n reflection\u00a0 in the water. When he was\r\n full, he threw himself on the other dog to steal his meat as well.\r\n Unfortunately, when he was in the water, he had to let go the remains of the\r\n meat to avoid drowning, and so was left with nothing.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Anjing yang serakah<br><br>suatu hari si anjing mencuri daging yang sangat besar, dan ia bangga karna itu. Lalu ia berlari sampai ia menapai sungai yang besar. Iamelihat ke air sungai dengan hati-hati. Lalu ia melihat anjing yang di mulutnya terdapat daging yang besar.<br>Lucunya, si aning tidak menyadari bahwa itu adalah pantulan dirinya sendiri.<br>Saat ia penuh, ia melempari dirinya sendiri ke anjing lainnya untuk mencuri daging milik si anjing itu. Sayangnya saat di air, ia melepaskan sisa-sisa daging agar tidak tenggelam. Jadi yang tertinggal tidak ada apa-apa<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "example-of-narrative-text-804",
            "question": "Example of narrative text",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Story of Aji Saka and Dewata Cengkar<br>\nMany, many years ago, the kingdom of Medangkamulan was ruled by a king \nnamed Dewata-chengkar. This king had a strange and frightening habit. He\n liked to eat human\u00a0 beings.<br>\nOne day, a young traveler arrived in the kingdom.He was called Ajisaka. \nAjisaka took shelter in the house of a widow who quickly came to look \nupon the young man as her own son. When he heard of the king&#039;s strange \nappetite, Ajisaka sympathized with the villagers&#039; plight and immediately\n volunteered to become the king&#039;s next meal.<br>\nAjisaka went directly to the king&#039;s palace.\u201cI am willing to be your next\n meal. Your Highnees. However, I have a request.\u201c said Aji Saka to the \nking. \u201cWhatever you please, young man, I will grant your request,\u201c the \nking replied. \u201cBefore you eat me, grant me some land. Just enough length\n of my own headcloth.\u201c continued Aji Saka. \u201cCome, Young Man. Let&#039;s \nmeasure your headcloth so that I can have my meal and you can have your \nland\u201c agreed the king.<br>\nAjisaka began to unwrap the cloth tied around his head. The king got \ndown from his throne and hold one end of the headcloth. He stepped \nbackward. What he didn&#039;t know was that this headcloth was much longer. \nThe king kept going backward, step by step, as the cloth kept \nunraveling. He stepped backward through the palace square, backward \nacross the village, holding the end of Ajisaka&#039;s headcloth. The king \nkept stepping backward until reached the sea cliftts of the sea.<br>\nA great crowd of people had gathered. They held their breath as their \nking took his final step backward over the cliff&#039;s edge and plunged into\n the waves crashing againts the rocks at the foot of the sea wall.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": ".The\u00a0 Origin of the city\u00a0 Surabaya<br><span>\n</span>\u00a0\u00a0 Once upon a time , there were two animals , Sura and Baya name . Sura \nis the name of the Beast is the Beast shark and Baya the crocodile . \nThey live in the deep sea . After Sura and Baya were looking for some \nfood . Suddenly, Baya see a nice goat . \" Yummy is good , this is the \nmost delicious lunch , \" said Baya . &#039; No way ! This is my lunch . You \ngreedy \" Sura said . Later they fought for goats . After several hours \nof fighting, they were very tired . Feels tired of fighting , they live \nin different places . Sura Baya live in the water and stay in the \ncountry.<br><br>\n\u00a0Border is the beach , so they do not will fight again . Someday , Sura \nwent to the ground and look for some food in the river . he was very \nhungry and there was not much food in the sea . Baya was very angry when\n he knew that Sura broke a promise . they fight again . They both \npunching and kicking . tail Sura Baya fight . Baya did the same thing to\n Sura . He bit very hard until Sura finally gave up and returned to the \nsea . Baya happy . named his final city of Surabaya .<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-dong-buatin-monologue-berbahasa-inggris-tentang-museum-p-871",
            "question": "Tolong dong buatin monologue berbahasa inggris tentang museum , pake opening sama closing juga .. :D",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Hi all, today I would like to share with all of you why I really in love with Museum, Why do I love with it?\u00a0First, Museum keeps all the civilization history of human being, from thousand years ago. When I went to my first museum, namely Louvre in Paris, I felt like I walked from 5000 years ago to recent moment. Second, Museum teach us how to be wise, it is due to the ability of Museum in conveying the story about war and its wisdom behind it. After all I recommend you to go to museum as often as possible.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "materi-tentang-giving-attention-the-speaker-please-dong-756",
            "question": "Materi tentang Giving, Attention the speaker????\r\n\r\n\r\nPlease dong......!!!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>Giving Attention</span><br>1.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0The Definition of Gaining AttentionGaining attention is a way or expression that is spoken so that other people will pay their attention to what we want to.2.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Expressions We Can Use to Ask Other People Attention\u00a0Here are some expressions we can use to ask aother people attention.1)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Attention, please!2)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0May/can I have your attention, please?3)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Look!4)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Look here!5)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Excuse me!6)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Excuse me, look here!7)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Listen to me, please.8)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0Waiter?9)\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0I\u2019m sorry, but \u2026.10)Wow, really?11)Excuse me, look here, please.12)I\u2019m listening.\u00a0Example :\u00a0<span>\u00a0Some of the examples by which you can showcase your keen attention to detail to the interviewer are:<br>1.\u00a0Talk about job role specifications and try understanding the deliverables. Ask questions.<br>2.\u00a0Try exhibiting your knowledge about the organization, the teams involved, the current market scenario and how the organization is trying to tackle the situations.<br>Lack of attention to detail<br>Lack of attention to detail is not really a good trait.<br>In fact, it is something that most of the employers look down upon. After all, no one wants to hire a lazy bum who pays no\u00a0attention to details!<br>How to improve attention to details<br>Anyone can improve his/her attention to details. All that is required is an intent and focus to achieve it. Perhaps, the best way to develop the trait is to start paying attention to things around you</span></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mohon-di-cek-benar-atau-salahnya-petunjuk-mengecek-1-kata-pert-716",
            "question": "Mohon di cek benar atau salahnya !    Petunjuk mengecek\r\n1. Kata pertama adalah pekerjaan\r\n2. Kata kedua adalah tempat bekerja\r\n3. Kata ketiga adalah aktivitas bekerja\r\nSoal\r\n1. Headmaster, school, manages the school\r\n2. Surgeon,\u00a0Hospital, operates on patiens\r\n3. Actress, Production house, acts on the stage\r\n4. Journalist, Newspaper, writes articles\r\n5. Driver, Travel agent, driver a bus\r\n6. Mechanic, Workshop, repairs car\r\n7. News reader, Radio station, reads the news\r\n8. Waiter, Restaurant, offers the menu\r\n9. Guide, Tourist agent, leads the tourist\r\n10. Cashier, Bank, serves the customer",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "semuanya bener kok ..",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "quote-one-sentence-spoken-by-the-characters-the-blue-elephant-321",
            "question": "Quote one sentence spoken by the characters ? The Blue Elephant",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I love The Blue Elephant!<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "why-world-is-full-english-why-english-language-becomes-an-inter-195",
            "question": "Why world is full english?\u00a0Why English language becomes an international language?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "because, languange english is languange connection all of country and many used by all people in the world<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "because English is can be unite of all language...",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "carikan-saya-pekerjaan-dan-ruangan-yang-ada-di-restaurant-dalam-415",
            "question": "Carikan saya pekerjaan dan\u00a0ruangan yang ada di restaurant dalam bahasa inggris mohon cepaaaaaaaaaat",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "pekerjaan : \"chef\"<br>ruangan \u00a0 \u00a0: \"kitchen\"",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "* waiter<br>*receptionist<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}